Zhi'an, run!
Release Zhu Huaijin
and I'll give you the Dragon Jade
You've kept this from me for so long
and still expect me to let him go?
In your dreams
No!
Since I'm here
I intend to give you the map
The map is on me
Don't!
Never thought right under my nose
such a devoted couple could emerge
Dying won't be that easy
The Dragon Jade treasure is on you
How about this
For every five steps Zhu Huaijin takes forward
you remove one piece of clothing
What do you say?
No! Absolutely not, Zhi'an!
Shut up
Not allowed
She loves you so much
You should just accept it
Fine
I promise you
Let's go
I won't go, I won't go
Don't, Zhi An
Take it off
You shouldn't have come
Even if it costs me my life, I'll get you out of here
I don't want you to die
I want you to live
Last piece
Take it off
Seventh Prince
You dare trick me
Kill
Kill! Kill!
Ruined my back
Thus the Dragon Jade Map shall never resurface
I underestimated you
All this began because of the Dragon Jade Map
I won't let those I love and who love me
Fall into danger again
Nor will I abandon Huaijin ever again
Do it
Does it hurt?
It's nothing compared to what you've sacrificed for me
You knew all along the Dragon Jade was behind you
You...
It seems Heaven
Has granted us both a chance to live again
So that's how it is
No wonder
I've been so cautious
Fearing you might get hurt again
But
You knew the truth all along
So it was you who stayed with me till my dying breath
Wasn't it?
Zhi An
Huai Chen, Zhi An
Is that you?
The one Zhi An married isn't Zhu Huai Chen, it's me
Zhi An
In the next life
May all this suffering
Fall upon me alone
It was Duan Yurou who killed you
Yet in this lifetime, I still failed to protect you
In our previous life
I was the one who killed him
You were reborn in your youth
You could have avoided all this
But got dragged into this vortex because of me
Even suffered torment
And became addicted to Five Minerals Powder
If I hadn't been constantly suspicious
and trusted you sooner
you could have suffered so much less
Don't talk about yourself like that
I just arrogantly thought I was protecting you completely
But I never considered
how terrified you must have been
when you saw me impersonating Zhu Huaichen
You were right not to trust me
Besides,
my worthless life didn't deserve your rescue
What do you mean 'worthless'?
You can't treat your own life so carelessly
All of us risked everything to save you
and you say it wasn't worth it?
Heaven gave you a second chance at life
and you're treating it with such contempt
I... my whole existence was for you
You should live for yourself
If you don't even value your own life
how can you talk about protecting me?
How could you just die like this without a care
Do you expect me to suffer alone for the rest of my life
Is this how you show your love for me
Zhi An
You... you to me
I didn't
You did
You said if I were to die
You would suffer for the rest of your life
You like me
You have feelings for me, don't you
You're right
My life isn't worthless
As long as you care about me
I'll live well
Even without me
You must keep living well
Just like how I would live well
Even without you
The most important thing in life is oneself
Since heaven has given us a second chance at life
We shouldn't dwell on past wounds and hatred
Once this matter is settled
I'd rather see
What you and I would be like
If we laid down our swords
This world is corrupt
Many choose to sink into depravity
Becoming accomplices to this era
Then someone must rise to overthrow it all
And remake the world anew
If the world were just
You, me, Duan Yurou
Even Zhu Huaichen
Might all have been different
Perhaps we'd have met amidst blooming flowers
Or crossed paths by mountains and lakes
The you back then
Would surely have had a different state of mind
And better understood your own worth
Then let me be the one to overturn everything
Zhi'an
Will you join me?
I will
There's still time to turn back
I still have a chance to turn back
Duan Yurou has left
Perhaps it's for the best
News came from the princess
The Li family's old allies are heading to the capital
They've finally come